— MEGAN PHILLIPS —

/ETERINARY PRACTICE SUPPORT

CONTACT

(760)965-9620

☐ megphillips21@gmail.com

PROFILE

I have spent 15 years in the veterinary industry, and in those years, I have worked in every department. I have a strong passion for the industry, and I would like to further my career in one of the many support positions that make practices run efficiently. I am self-motivated, driven, and thrive on challenges. I have been actively taking on jobs that no one else wanted, simply to learn why no one wants them. This approach has given me experience with inventory, retail product management, accounts receivable, difficult clients, and all IT problems.

SKILLS

- FXPFRIFNCED RVT
- NETWORK ADMIN
- VOIP PHONE
- PROFICIENT IN IMPROMED,
 AVIMARK, CORNERSTONE
- INVENTORY MANAGEMENT

EDUCATION

Colorado State University

2009

Bachelor's Animal Science-Equine Science

San Juan College

2016

Associates in Veterinary Technology

Google IT Support Certificate

Currently Attending

EXPERIENCE

Bishop Veterinary Hospital

2013- Present Operations Manager

I am currently the operations manager for Bishop Veterinary Hospital. We are a 4 location, mixed animal practice in rural CA. I lead a team that moved the practice from full paper records to a tech lead paper lite system. I spent time in every department and every location before moving into my current position. I was tasked with finding creative solutions to challenging issues. Rebuilt codes, bundles, electronic forms, workflows, consent forms, etc. Implemented VOIP phones, patient portal, integrated lab and imaging, scanning software, and google workspace.

Garden Valley Veterinary Hospital

2010-2013 Veterinary Technician

Worked as a veterinary technician for a two doctor small animal practice. During this time in my career, I learned and honed my skills as a technician. I used my time at this small practice to learn as much as I could. Due to its small size, we did not have departments, we got to do it all and I soaked in as much as possible. I left due to a relocation of my husband.

Arvada Veterinary Hospital

2009-2010 Client Service Representative

Worked as CSR in a five doctor, small animal practice. During this time, I fulfilled all client service duties. This was a very tech forward clinic, and I learned so much that I brought with me to other clinics. I discovered that I enjoy the client portion of veterinary medicine as much as I enjoyed the patient aspect. My time here was short, but only because opportunity for a technician position presented itself.